<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Kryptos</string>

    <string name="large_string">
        Pellentesque et volutpat quam. Phasellus lectus nibh, tincidunt sed mattis at, facilisis non justo. Nulla
        dapibus tellus vel turpis varius, at varius est congue. Nulla cursus, lacus vel condimentum ornare, tortor nulla
        dapibus eros, vel vulputate mi dui a lorem. Nam a turpis nisi. Nam pulvinar faucibus mauris. Vivamus nec magna
        eu felis commodo eleifend vel id ligula. Etiam velit sem, lacinia ut tellus ut, interdum porttitor risus. Class
        aptent taciti sociosqu ad litora torquent per conubia nostra, per inceptos himenaeos. Morbi scelerisque blandit
        nisi, molestie pellentesque arcu sagittis et. In ultricies, neque ac sagittis feugiat, arcu nibh auctor nisi, et
        vehicula velit nunc in lacus.

        Donec vitae dui eu libero tristique luctus id nec leo. Sed sit amet mollis eros. Pellentesque eu metus libero.
        Vestibulum non est nunc. Suspendisse at enim vel quam tincidunt posuere ac in turpis. Ut accumsan magna id felis
        accumsan, nec vestibulum risus feugiat. Nulla sit amet feugiat metus. In sed dui risus.

        Integer in mi quis enim mattis feugiat auctor non erat. Aliquam lacinia ut ex vitae lacinia. Nullam nulla ipsum,
        suscipit in dui non, efficitur pulvinar metus. Nullam id enim metus. Suspendisse sed metus sapien. Quisque
        commodo feugiat tincidunt. Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis
        egestas. In ac vestibulum urna, at hendrerit lorem. Fusce ac convallis enim, sed tempor massa. Sed sed feugiat
        augue. Donec ultrices metus urna, sed scelerisque ex rutrum sed.

        Fusce blandit sapien eu sagittis eleifend. Nam blandit interdum felis, tempor gravida turpis feugiat id. Donec
        in turpis ac lacus suscipit dictum nec non arcu. Orci varius natoque penatibus et magnis dis parturient montes,
        nascetur ridiculus mus. Mauris consequat mauris aliquet turpis egestas porttitor eget in turpis. Donec tristique
        odio ac pretium malesuada. Maecenas eu lorem dapibus, laoreet diam et, blandit mi. Sed gravida elit vitae nunc
        fermentum, nec venenatis justo tincidunt. Aenean vel blandit sapien, sodales molestie arcu. Nunc nec ipsum ac
        augue blandit blandit ut sit amet ipsum. Vestibulum elementum iaculis urna non elementum.

        Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Ut odio tellus,
        bibendum et ultricies dictum, varius eu lorem. In volutpat consectetur iaculis. Sed venenatis sapien a accumsan
        scelerisque. Suspendisse potenti. Etiam finibus dapibus nunc, a consectetur justo aliquet sed. Curabitur
        hendrerit libero id sapien faucibus luctus.

        Aenean ac lacus eu metus viverra viverra. Cras lectus elit, egestas quis facilisis in, dictum sed leo. Maecenas
        massa neque, lacinia vitae mauris posuere, porttitor efficitur sapien. Pellentesque sollicitudin sapien nec
        aliquet malesuada. Pellentesque sed interdum nisl, at aliquet ligula. Nam tincidunt, arcu ut auctor convallis,
        nibh lorem imperdiet arcu, sed pretium mauris ipsum quis urna. Nulla et ante lobortis, maximus mi id, imperdiet
        felis. Nunc gravida, metus at bibendum posuere, elit ante consectetur metus, nec ornare turpis sem ac arcu.
        Integer sem elit, iaculis sed pharetra sed, volutpat eu ipsum.

        Nullam vel purus consequat, efficitur purus et, condimentum dolor. Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique
        senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Aliquam lacinia ipsum sed orci ornare, non convallis
        odio cursus. Nam eu dui sit amet dolor dapibus finibus. Nulla aliquam felis lacus, eu dictum leo laoreet in.
        Cras varius, tortor nec vulputate placerat, quam nisi tempor quam, vel dapibus libero justo eget ante. Praesent
        ornare ut enim vitae pellentesque. Sed elementum odio dolor, nec blandit elit vestibulum sed. Ut fermentum arcu
        ut lacus condimentum, non eleifend tellus blandit. Donec tincidunt mauris ut volutpat commodo. Etiam semper non
        ante non imperdiet. Pellentesque mauris augue, maximus quis tellus nec, consectetur rhoncus odio. Nulla molestie
        efficitur diam consectetur aliquam. Nullam hendrerit consectetur nisi varius ultricies. Donec non neque
        convallis, mattis quam semper, consequat augue.
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_scrolling">ScrollingActivity</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"

        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
        "The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, "
        "interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"

        "Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n"

        "The foundational elements of print based design typography, grids, space, scale, color, "
        "and use of imagery guide visual treatments. These elements do far more than please the "
        "eye. They create hierarchy, meaning, and focus. Deliberate color choices, edge to edge "
        "imagery, large scale typography, and intentional white space create a bold and graphic "
        "interface that immerse the user in the experience.\n"
        "An emphasis on user actions makes core functionality immediately apparent and provides "
        "waypoints for the user.\n\n"

        "Motion provides meaning.\n\n"

        "Motion respects and reinforces the user as the prime mover. Primary user actions are "
        "inflection points that initiate motion, transforming the whole design.\n"
        "All action takes place in a single environment. Objects are presented to the user without "
        "breaking the continuity of experience even as they transform and reorganize.\n"
        "Motion is meaningful and appropriate, serving to focus attention and maintain continuity. "
        "Feedback is subtle yet clear. Transitions are efﬁcient yet coherent.\n\n"

        "3D world.\n\n"

        "The material environment is a 3D space, which means all objects have x, y, and z "
        "dimensions. The z-axis is perpendicularly aligned to the plane of the display, with the "
        "positive z-axis extending towards the viewer. Every sheet of material occupies a single "
        "position along the z-axis and has a standard 1dp thickness.\n"
        "On the web, the z-axis is used for layering and not for perspective. The 3D world is "
        "emulated by manipulating the y-axis.\n\n"

        "Light and shadow.\n\n"

        "Within the material environment, virtual lights illuminate the scene. Key lights create "
        "directional shadows, while ambient light creates soft shadows from all angles.\n"
        "Shadows in the material environment are cast by these two light sources. In Android "
        "development, shadows occur when light sources are blocked by sheets of material at "
        "various positions along the z-axis. On the web, shadows are depicted by manipulating the "
        "y-axis only. The following example shows the card with a height of 6dp.\n\n"

        "Resting elevation.\n\n"

        "All material objects, regardless of size, have a resting elevation, or default elevation "
        "that does not change. If an object changes elevation, it should return to its resting "
        "elevation as soon as possible.\n\n"

        "Component elevations.\n\n"

        "The resting elevation for a component type is consistent across apps (e.g., FAB elevation "
        "does not vary from 6dp in one app to 16dp in another app).\n"
        "Components may have different resting elevations across platforms, depending on the depth "
        "of the environment (e.g., TV has a greater depth than mobile or desktop).\n\n"

        "Responsive elevation and dynamic elevation offsets.\n\n"

        "Some component types have responsive elevation, meaning they change elevation in response "
        "to user input (e.g., normal, focused, and pressed) or system events. These elevation "
        "changes are consistently implemented using dynamic elevation offsets.\n"
        "Dynamic elevation offsets are the goal elevation that a component moves towards, relative "
        "to the component’s resting state. They ensure that elevation changes are consistent "
        "across actions and component types. For example, all components that lift on press have "
        "the same elevation change relative to their resting elevation.\n"
        "Once the input event is completed or cancelled, the component will return to its resting "
        "elevation.\n\n"

        "Avoiding elevation interference.\n\n"

        "Components with responsive elevations may encounter other components as they move between "
        "their resting elevations and dynamic elevation offsets. Because material cannot pass "
        "through other material, components avoid interfering with one another any number of ways, "
        "whether on a per component basis or using the entire app layout.\n"
        "On a component level, components can move or be removed before they cause interference. "
        "For example, a floating action button (FAB) can disappear or move off screen before a "
        "user picks up a card, or it can move if a snackbar appears.\n"
        "On the layout level, design your app layout to minimize opportunities for interference. "
        "For example, position the FAB to one side of stream of a cards so the FAB won’t interfere "
        "when a user tries to pick up one of cards.\n\n"
    </string>

    <string name="advanced_bttom_sheet_behavior">com.hayashibambi.kryptos.AdvancedBottomSheetBehavior</string>
    <string name="whack_a_mole_behavior">com.hayashibambi.kryptos.WhackAMoleBehavior</string>
</resources>
